One in every 12 people in
the world owns a firearm.
What we gotta do
is work out some way to get
the other 11 to buy one too.
Especially in China
1.3... 1.3 billion people in China.
Well, actually arms sales
are banned under Chinese law.
But I heard that the insurance fee
for "dwelling in the Fuchun mountains"
scroll is as high as 1 billion yuan.
Oh, really!
The boss deeply appreciate
the word "reunion"?
Which is set to triple the
value of the painting.
Take them off, now!
Somebody got there first.
You know what to do next.
Yes.
Dwelling in the Fuchun
mountains is in our hands.
The expression of ink within
a square implies a painting.
The strokes in the middle means water.
And the part at the bottom means fire.
Fire in conflict with water.
Empress, is this about "dwelling
in the Fuchun mountains"?
The half of "dwelling in the
Fuchun mountains" in Taipei
was stolen last night.
Please contact Hong Kong HQ.
Huang Gongwang created it
during the Yuan dynasty.
It's one of the ten most important
paintings in Chinese history.
During the Ming dynasty
it was burnt and torn in two.
One half is now in the Taipei
National Palace Museum
in Taiwan
the other half is in the
Zhejiang Museum in China.
After 361 years apart
the two halves of the legendary.
Dwelling in the Fuchun mountains painting
will be brought together for the first time
at an exhibition
at the Taipei National
Palace Museum next June.
The event will attract global attention?
Once it is announced.
However, the Taiwan half
was suddenly stolen last night.
If we cannot locate it quickly
there will be unimaginable consequences.
The police in China, Hong Kong and Taiwan?
Have formed a joint task force
to conduct the "switch operation"
under the leadership of F.
Sir, we've secured half of the scroll
taken from Taiwan.
What should we do?
Bring it back.
Ok.
The Taiwan operation was
a complete failure.
4 sisters were killed
and we lost the painting.
My grandfather died for this painting
in the pacific war?
Yes, master.
Your father kept this forgery
to remember your grandfather's sacrifice.
Mmm, baby!
Sir, your drink!
Oh, thank you!
How is it?
The best drink I ever had!
Your vacation in Dubai is over.
Move your ass!
West lake is like heaven for men
I want to go to the amusement park.
Be a good boy.
Darling, give mom a kiss
I want to go to the amusement park.
We have our own fun ride right here.
Be careful, don't drop him.
Now we're flying under the radar
I'm flying! I'm flying!
Your bossy half, Lin Yuyan, is here.
No problem.
She makes my cover story more real
Nick!
Good to see you here!
Let me help you.
Look what I bought you.
Any clues?
Not yet.
Stay focused.
Uncover their plan
Nick is hard to crack.
Several years I haven't seen you
but still messing around
with girls, isn't it.
Absolutely!
She's hot, man!
She puts your pants on fire!
You are damned right!
You should've stopped her!
Sweetie, always be prepared.
Who is she?
One of my women!
Oh no!
Xiao Jinhan, male.
Born in Hong Kong in 1971.
Received a doctorate in law at Cambridge.
Officially,
he's a lawyer with P & T.
Actually,
he's probably a Hong Kong
smuggling-seizing agent.
Hello everybody, we have
a suspect for the theft?
In Taipei.
We believe that the other half of
the painting in Hangzhou
is their next target.
We have to completely lock it down.
Let me introduce you.
This is Lin Yuyan
from the insurance agency PICC.
Hello, everyone!
The Hangzhou half of the scroll
is insured for us $160 million.
Of course, it's actually priceless.
Over the next 72 hours,
we'll set our best team
and state-of-the-art systems
to secure the Hangzhou Museum.
So, you have the Taiwan
half of the painting?
And?
Name your price.
One doesn't sell a single shoe.
A pair has greater value.
Sorry, can I sit here?
Yes, please sit!
Thank you!
Make way for the empress!
Who is she?
She is the host of this banquet.
We call her the empress.
What's with the hourglass?
I've no idea. It's weird.
This sand is all that remains of
my dear dead husband.
For 50 years,
he tormented me.
But who'd have imagined?
I outlived him.
Now his bones and soul belong to me
I can turn him to face heaven or face hell.
Empress
shall we begin?
Of course, of course, of course!
Let the show begin!
When we were young,
and the world was younger too,
people got married before having babies,
doctors still worked to heal,
people still wore clothes in photographs,
debts are still paid,
fathers needn't check
their child's paternity,
F says...
The empress is not your target
cats and rats, were still foes
I hear that you like magic.
That's your card.
This is my card.
Who are you?
That is not important.
Most important is that what I want
no one can touch.
Fuck you!
I touch what I want, I take what I want.
There's nothing you can do about it.
How about a game?
If you win, I return to Tokyo.
If I win
you go back to wherever you came from.
Perfect
I never lose.
Let's play!
Guess how many fingers on my left hand?
5.
You lose.
4 fingers.
What kind of fucked up game is this anyway?
It's hot in here.
Are you boys having fun?
You're here for it too, right?
What are you getting at?
The Hangzhou half doesn't interest you?
That's none of your business.
You already lost the Taipei half.
You don't want to lose this half, do you?
I can help you secure it.
And then I can make a fortune.
Money is not a problem.
The Hangzhou half will be transported
from the museum to the vault
by boat.
It's ready!
Everyone, step back.
Fresh popcorn.
Try some.
This is the latest innovation in security.
The microwave firewall.
Not even a mosquito can breach it,
let alone a human being.
We guarantee it's 100% secure.
Commissioner Kong...
Good job!
What?
Please reconsider?
Commissioner!
The system's perfect.
Why are we moving the painting?
Who will take responsibility?
I'll take it from here.
The painting is being escorted
by a convoy of cars, not by boat.
It's misdirection. That's their so-called
"switch operation"
I'm just passing the Southern bridge
approaching the wetland park.
Handsome guys!
Handsome guys! Look here!
Look here!
What's going on?
What's mine is mine!
The cat is just like me.
It wants it's cream at any cost.
Get me the painting.
Be ready in my room.
Pay your respects
I can't
I can't.
Mother, I can't.
The empress has the painting.
She'll trade with Yamamoto in Tokyo.
"Should I take action
against the empress now?"
Okay. See you in Tokyo.
"No, wait for the right moment."
Have you considered the consequences of
making a move without permission?
We can't miss this chance.
Why has my partner tonight been changed?
We can't use
our own guy tonight.
But you're a lucky devil.
Your date is a long-legged beauty.
But she seems to know
your jealous little angel lin Yuyan.
A beauty sounds good.
But I'm not really a legs man.
Whether a woman is beautiful or not
has nothing to do with her long legs.
See what I mean?
I'm happy to hear that.
Do I make the grade?
Welcome to
the Chando charitable auction ball.
Tonight's highlight
is a limited edition
of Chando expo-edition pure nutrient cream.
It includes secret ingredients
taken from 5000 feet above
the Himalaya mountains.
Now we start the bidding!
20,000!
26,000!
26,000. Any higher?
35,000!
45,000!
50,000!
50,000. Are there any more bids?
Okay! Sold!
Scotch on the rocks!
Okay!
Just make it two.
Yes.
Why are you staring at my cleavage?
It looks attractive.
Cheers!
Why not ask me about the necklace?
Someone asked you to wear
the jewelry I gave her.
It's to scare me away.
Spot on. 10 points!
And a bonus question.
What will I do?
You are going to seduce me first
and then sell me out.
Perfect score. Another 10 points.
Let's get to work.
Testing... testing... say something
I love you!
Thank you!
I have no resistance to seduction,
don't say you love me unless you mean it.
I may marry you and stick with you
for the rest of your life.
All I want is your heart.
My heart is fully booked.
9 o'clock.
10 meters ahead.
Release your hormones on the control panel.
What's happening?
Fuck it!
Check it out!
Check it! Be quick! Be quick!
Good job!
Thank you.
You're off now.
And where are you heading?
A paradise for men
to lose their troubles
or gain more.
Your trouble is waiting for you at home,
isn't she?
A man's courage in his ignorance,
a girl's pleasure in hers.
Tell my wife that the less she knows
the happier she will be.
Xiao stole it. What's our next step?
It's a trap. Get out!
Go!
Speak up.
Do you have the painting?
Of course!
We've just been told that
the drop-point has changed
I'm here.
Strike, 9 o'clock.
Strike, strike.
It's a trap. Get out!
It's a trap. Strike, 9 o'clock.
We have the painting.
Should we kill him?
Death is such a predictable quick outcome.
Endless suffering has a
more tasteful flavor.
But we should leave him
something to remember us by.
Plunge a knife
into his heart
and he'll share
in my torment.
Blood type a.
Who are you?
PICC's Lin Yuyan...
Lin Yuyan... Lin Yuyan
I'm flying! I'm flying!
"Hong Kong, 3 months later."
You're so lucky
Lisa died at your hands.
And 4 other agents
were killed for nothing.
But it insisted we release you.
But you've vanished. You
no longer exist on earth
understand?
You're a ghost.
Xiao Jinhan and Ms. Wang Xueqing
had a car accident
during a business trip to Japan.
They are both deceased.
You still belong to us.
You go where you're told to go
live a simple life.
It's also for the safety
of your family.
So women are happiest in the kitchen.
You?
Pig.
Get out!
I burned all the eggs.
You can only have this.
No!
No, really!
What's wrong?
What is it?
Quickly, get up!
1... 2... 3!
Better?
I'm allergic to duck eggs.
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't give me the chance
I'll get used to them.
Just give me some time.
"The truth will be revealed."
What are the knots for?
To count time.
A knot for every day I'm here.
1, 2, 3.
Why do you eat duck eggs like candy.
To cure myself.
You always look unhappy
you don't like it here?
I like this place very much.
Will you leave us?
I don't want you to go.
Talk to my father
and ask permission to marry me.
Silly!
I'm your Uncle
I don't need an Uncle.
In 6 years, I'll be 18.
Then I'll marry you for sure.
Do you like the lady?
In black in the photo?
Do you miss her?
I know what it feels like.
It hurts.
My mother died 8 years ago
I miss her every day.
Every time I hear a boat
I think she's coming home.
But it's never her.
And now I hardly even see her in my dreams.
Why are you so sad.
She's still alive.
If she can cure you
I'll let her have you.
Shall we play a game?
Excuse me
are you Miss Lin Yuyan?
I am.
Come with me.
Where?
Beijing head office.
Please, this way.
Please, take a seat.
Thank you.
The joint exhibition opens
in 10 days.
There's been no progress
in the investigation.
According to information
provided by the police...
The half we took from Xiao Jinhan
is a fake.
Xiao Jinhan, Xiao Jinhan.
An enemy that is my match
has not yet been born.
Someone was here.
Right
I found this.
"Name: Xiao Jinhan position:."
"Ex-ISSB agent."
"Current mission: Switch operation."
"Marriott fish head bar,
9 o'clock tomorrow evening."
"Once the painting is reunited,
the family will also be."
I knew you would leave one day
I'm in position.
The things you asked for
I ordered online.
Are you Ms. Lin Yuyan?
Yes.
Jindong express delivery, please sign
I'm on an airplane
I'm flying!
You're a cheeky monkey.
You're getting too heavy. Quick,
come down off your Uncle.
Postman!
Quick!
Quick.
It's express?
Yes.
Xiao Jinhan is back.
He must want the other half of the scroll.
You broke his heart
when you died in front of him in Tokyo.
You should make it up to him.
It's dangerous here.
The car is waiting.
Please come again.
"Buy me, or offer me a job,."
"Rmblo, 10,000 plus a month."
You look a lot like my next boyfriend.
You look a lot like my dead ex-girlfriend.
If I can be your girlfriend
I don't mind being a ghost.
"Wang Xueqing belongs to Yamamoto;
Her death was faked."
"Commence the switch operation,
but don't alert the enemy."
A whole night
and we've got nothing.
You should eat something.
Thank you.
If you want to take a nap
I'll keep watching.
Someone's out there!
Xiao Jinhan!
Come with me!
Say something!
Stop it!
You're allergic to duck eggs!
Like I said
I can overcome it
I did it
I'm sorry.
Hubbie.
Why didn't you invite me to join you?
How was I?
Pretty convincing, huh?
Yes.
What do you want?
I know that you have the painting.
Cheers!
And I also know that
you have a son called Baobao.
Right?
So what?
A national treasure or
your family treasure.
You can only save one.
Young man
where is Baobao?
Over there.
For you!
Baobao, Baobao.
Your mother is here.
Come along.
"Baobao has arrived safely."
Tell Xiao Jinhan
to bring back my scroll.
You know the consequences
if you call the police.
Yuyan?
Baobao has been kidnapped!
I know.
It must be Yamamoto.
How do you know?
Who are you?
Where have you been these days?
Now's not the right time to explain.
They want to exchange
the painting for Baobao
I don't care how you treat me.
But I want my son back
I want my son
I beg you.
Please help me
hello?
Who's this?
Shut up!
Hello?
Who was that?
"Meet at the Umbrella museum."
Go home and wait for me
I'm going with you.
Okay. Okay then.
The number you are calling is powered off.
"Yamamoto will exchange."
"Baobao for the painting."
"Xiao Jinhan, tomorrow
at 3pm, Xiangji temple."
"Think of the whole
picture, don't act rashly."
"Tell Xiao Jinhan,"
"4 pm at Pinghu Autumn Moon teahouse."
"Yuyan, trust me."
"I'll save Baobao."
"Tell Xiao Jinhan, 5pm at 3 pools
mirroring the moon island."
"Xiao Jinhan, 7pm, impression west lake."
"Our patience is running out."
So sorry
for frightening you.
Even though you weren't invited
I knew you'd come.
Give me my son back!
An educated woman
shouldn't speak to a gentleman like that.
Furthermore
I don't think you have any leverage
I have the painting.
No, it's with Xiao Jinhan.
Let's wait for him to join us for dinner.
He won't come.
Oh, he will.
Mrs. Xiao.
The latest fashion from Paris.
Help Mrs. Xiao get dressed
I have Baobao
I believe you will not be so stupid
that you fight against me.
Very beautiful!
Paris is heaven for women
even it's music has the taste of beauty.
Do you recognize this?
As far as I know,
all stolen property is evidence.
Chatty women are not attractive.
This ancient Chinese torture instrument
is for extracting eyeballs.
In the past
killing was an art form
at the cutting edge of innovation.
But first
let's eat.
There's still no sign of Xiao Jinhan.
Go to save Guihua
say sorry
Chinese pig!
Say sorry
Mom!
Mommy, help me! Mommy!
Put down your weapons! Let them go!
Mom!
Mommy! Help me!
Mommy!
What took you so long.
Get on board.
So that's why they call you the empress
I'm so impressed
I can get the painting out
of the country for you.
And why should I believe you?
We've been doing business for years.
Besides, you have no other option.
We can make delivery in Dubai.
Perhaps I can also get the other half
I'll be in touch.
Money is no object.
Go home and rest.
We have everything under control.
Thanks
I didn't expect
you would trade the painting for my Baobao.
My world only makes sense
when you're both safe.
Baobao!
Mommy!
Baby
are you hurting?
Hi. What would you like to have?
You know what I want.
Sure!
Is that it?
The British are willing to
sell their half of the painting.
The empress has already set up the meeting.
Here you go.
Tell the empress
my master is waiting for the other half.
Nice body!
Hi.
Welcome, sir. Please.
Please.
Welcome.
Hello.
So far from home.
You must be lonely.
This should keep you busy.
Welcome to the Atlantis.
Thank you.
Hello!
You're welcome to the Atlantis palm Dubai.
It's a real pleasure to have you.
"The painting."
"Yamamoto got is fake."
"The original half stolen"
"in Taipei is possessed by British."
"Complete your mission and bring it back."
Lisa is staying in the royal suite
of the Atlantis palm Dubai.
The painting is in the
safe box in the study.
The British already have their eyes on it
I understand
ls your heart racing?
Please excuse me for not be able to see it.
If I can touch it.
Maybe I can answer you.
Don't you want the other
half of the painting?
Both halves will soon be in front of us.
But whom will it belong to?
It belongs to it's true owner.
Who holds it is the owner.
That's the logic of some Japanese.
But you are still Chinese.
Apart from women
weapons are the only toys for men.
Have you found a buyer?
Yes, a Chinese lady is waiting.
You check her out yet?
The empress sent her.
Alright then.
So.
You're interested in the
"Fuchun mountains" painting?
Yes.
Well, it's gonna cost you.
What the hell is that?
Sorry
ladies first.
No.
There's a problem.
That's right.
The problem is you.
Someone has broken into
your khalif a vault.
Who the fuck do they think they are?
Well, James will take care of them.
It looks like you're not the only one
that's interested in that painting.
Go!
Let's go!
Jump!
Go!
How's your wound. Let me see it.
The British are coming.
Can you walk?
Quickly!
Go!
Say something.
Say what?
Say anything.
No matter the truth or a lie
I prefer the truth.
Lying is tiring.
What makes you stay with Yamamoto?
I need to be loved.
Can you give me that
I am not used to a tertium quid.
But I don't care.
Get some rest
I'll be back tomorrow.
Are you still in pain?
There's a fine line
between flirting and love
just as between life and death.
You crossed that line
so Xiao Jinhan has to pay the price.
What will you do to him?
Can't you at least
hide your feelings for him in front of me?
I won't let you touch him.
Don't worry.
He's safe for today
I need him to lead me
to the scroll tomorrow.
You're too melodramatic. The game's over.
You know you are the only woman that
I love in this world.
You cannot betray me.
That's not love.
Because I resemble your mother
must I also die at your hands
I just remembered that
your younger brother
is graduating from Harvard soon.
We should attend the ceremony together.
Clear up this mess.
We shouldn't disappoint him
I'll wait for you back
so that we can all celebrate
your birthday together
I believe you know how to use this.
In ten seconds, it can
take Xiao Jinhan to heaven.
He won't feel a thing.
You're awake.
Is it your birthday today?
My birthday is a few days away
but I may not live to see it
God loves everyone
not just you.
If you still want someone to love you only,
heaven is not the right place for you.
You must think that I'm cheap.
No.
Everyone will get their favorites
with no regret.
But you'd make the wrong choice.
It is judge by me.
This will be a secret
if we agreed not to disclosure
I need to ask my wife
I feel pity for you
because your duty will
bury you with sorrow.
Let's change the subject.
Let's talk about your future
and your dreams?
I don't have a future
I've been living a nightmare for years
I remember the day you stabbed me.
Lying on the floor, I heard
you crying out to me
I was so moved.
That night
I had my only sweet dream.
You whispered in my ear
that you'd take me to a place
free of nightmares.
Hello
ls me.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to the airport
I'll return the scroll to China.
You'll be safer without it.
Take it easy.
I will see you at the airport.
Hello?
Yuyan!
Sorry!
Sorry, Xiao Jinhan
I heard you and Lisa talking yesterday
I just want to ask you one thing.
If we had no son
would you still choose me?
It won't open!
You haven't answered my question yet.
Yuyan
for me
love is not a choice.
Now, we're safe.
The British must be
convinced of our deaths.
You're really 3 moves
ahead of everyone.
It's all part of the
"switch operation" plan.
Quick, check the painting.
Give me some time.
Be happy together.
Move even a few steps from me
and the alarm sounds.
You're not going anywhere
without my permission.
Where is Xiao Jinhan?
He must have gone to
Yamamoto to get the scroll.
Yamamoto is expecting him.
Only you can save him now.
Why should I?
Because you love him
I'll go with you.
If you go, it's a death wish.
If I die
I give him to you.
I don't even have the right
to give him to anybody.
Nor do I.
The only man that truly belongs to me
is my son
I just have my younger brother.
He's the only family I have left.
A woman only lives for her man.
Do you think any man knows that?
Xiao Jinhan understands.
We meet again.
It seems that you really want to
take everything I treasure.
Not only the painting
but the only woman I love.
Marriage is just
a legal contract
trading money for sex.
But true love is different.
Like this painting
I can only love something
unique in the world.
What I want you can not touch.
You can never possess
what doesn't belong to you
not even a grain of sand
or a drop of water.
What I've taken is mine
I'd like to see how you
can take it from me.
Go for Yamamoto.
Let me handle everything here.
You even betrayed Yamamoto for Xiao Jinhan.
There's no way out
I can not choose who I live for
I can choose who I die for
I really wanted to be a
bride once in my life
and give you a daughter.
Let me be your only choice in our next life
Lisa!
Wake up!
Why did you have to do that?
She was the only reason for me to live.
And you've taken her from me.
Let's have fate determine
who is going to live.
Give me back the painting.
Let's now toast to the
successful joint exhibition of.
Dwelling in the Fuchun mountains.
Cheers!
Ms. Lin
you are picc's project director
and a true hero behind the scenes
of this joint exhibition.
You experienced so many dangerous incidents
to realize it's success
what left you with the
strongest impression?
I'm very thrilled
to be here today
at the Taipei National Palace Museum
to witness the two national
treasures reunited
after more than
3-and-a-half centuries.
"Once the painting is reunited,
the family will also be."
Surely it isn't here?
How can it be here at this public event.
Understood.
F asked me to deliver this to you.
Once the painting is reunited,
the family will also be.
The high quality forgery of
the Hangzhou half of the scroll
is the greatest triumph
of my life as an artist.
The Japanese and the British
can't tell the difference between
the real and the fake anyway.
Before the joint exhibition in Taipei
the empress refused to
let the real painting
leave the Hangzhou museum.
Your father exchanged
this painting for you.
My father knew it was a fake
from the very beginning.
He told me that after scanning the painting
with the latest technology
he can distinguish even a 0.01%
difference between them.
He dreams that I can grow up
to become a great hi-tech detective.
Mommy! Mommy!
What is this?
Have a try.
No.
He's allergic to duck eggs
just like his father.
Duty calls.
My birthday is a few days away
but I may not
live to see it
Lisa told me that
she dreamed of being a bride